♪ ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, RIDING
AROUND IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, IF YOU
LIVE THE LIFE YOU PLEASE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT,
DOING THE BEST YOU CAN ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, AS
LONG AS YOU LEND A HAND ♪
♪ YOU CAN SIT AROUND AND
WAIT FOR THE PHONE TO RING ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ WAITING FOR SOMEONE
TO TELL YOU EVERYTHING ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ SIT AROUND AND WONDER
WHAT TOMORROW WILL BRING ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, EVEN
IF THEY SAY YOU'RE WRONG ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, SOMETIMES
YOU GOTTA BE STRONG ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, AS LONG
AS YOU GOT SOMEWHERE TO LAY ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT,
EVERYDAY IS JUDGMENT DAY ♪
♪ MAYBE SOMEWHERE
DOWN THE ROAD AWAYS ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ YOU'LL THINK OF ME, WONDER
WHERE I AM THESE DAYS ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ MAYBE SOMEWHERE DOWN THE
ROAD WHEN SOMEBODY PLAYS ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ PURPLE HAZE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, EVEN
WHEN PUSH COMES TO SHOVE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, IF
YOU GOT SOMEONE TO LOVE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT,
EVERYTHING'LL WORK OUT FINE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, WE'RE
GOING TO THE END OF THE LINE ♪
♪ DON'T HAVE TO BE ASHAMED
OF THE CAR I DRIVE ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ I'M GLAD TO BE HERE,
HAPPY TO BE ALIVE ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ IT DON'T MATTER IF
YOU'RE BY MY SIDE ♪
♪ (AT THE END OF THE LINE) ♪
♪ I'M SATISFIED ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, EVEN
IF YOU'RE OLD AND GRAY ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, YOU STILL
GOT SOMETHING TO SAY ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, REMEMBER
TO LIVE AND LET LIVE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, THE BEST
YOU CAN DO IS FORGIVE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, RIDING
AROUND IN THE BREEZE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, IF YOU
LIVE THE LIFE YOU PLEASE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, EVEN
IF THE SUN DON'T SHINE ♪
♪ WELL IT'S ALL RIGHT, WE'RE
GOING TO THE END OF THE LINE ♪
♪ ♪